TAP TAP What is a temporary
ПВР ПВР Это что такое пункт временного
accommodation center I mean, you
размещения В смысле вас
were evacuated yes and where did you live before this
эвакуировали да а а где жили до этого
Belgorod
Белгородской
Region
области
Belgorod Grandfather hello hello well you were
Белгородский Дед привет привет ну тебя
wondering where the boiler Yes where is the boiler department
интересовало где котл Да где котл отд
Olguin My God And what is it 200 2,000 or
Ольгин Боже мой И что там 200 2.000 или
whatever you said 20,000 20,000 said
сколько ты говорил 20.000 20.000 говорил
yes  you are a group of 2,000 So wait, this
да ты группировка 2.000 Так подожди это
was 2 weeks ago, you and I talked.
было 2 недели назад мы с тобой общались
This was the boiler more than a month ago, so
Это было котёл более месяца назад так
this is where the results of that boiler are.
вот и что это где результаты того котла
And the question is, they are slowly letting you
А вопрос-то туда потихонечку впускают
back in. No, so wait, well, how did you and I
обратно нет Так подожди ну как мы с
communicate? This is two weeks ago  you
тобой общались Это недели две назад ты
said everything there, the cauldron, where is this cauldron,
говорил всё там котёл то где этот котёл
where are these captives who died, where is Olginka
где эти пленные погибшие где Ольгинка Ну
Well, where are all these people, captives, who
так где все эти люди пленные
died there? 20,000 you said in the cauldron.
погибшие там 20.000 ты говорил в котле
There they remain there. Well, you said,
Там они там и остаются Ну ты говорил 20
20,000 in the cauldron.
000 в котле Да Слушай ну ты дурнее не
said how many two or
Кажись Ну ты говорил сколько две или
20,000 two you said 20,000 I thought it was
20.000 две ты говорил 20.000 я считал
like, what is this for Listen, I’ll
типа что это для Слушай я сейчас
switch now, you’ll get it for me Ay, it’s burnt, it’s
переключись ты мне доста Ай подгорел
burnt,
подгорел
well, listen, let’s talk normally,
ну слушай давай Давай нормально
look at it completely, look like this Wait
смотри ждн полностью смотри так Подожди
Now, that’s it, let’s get the boilers, that’s all I understand the
Сейчас всё давай котлы это всё Я понимаю
boilers and cook everything there  porridge Listen, there
котлы и всё сварите там каши Слушай вот
were elections in Moldova, you don’t want
выборы в Молдове был не хочешь
to confirm, yes
потверждает да
So you’re still peregaz Desh not no peregaz I’ll
Так ты ж всё перега Деш не не перегаз я
be here Okay, how will they be, let’s
буду вот Ладно как они будут давай
try it, let’s ask
попробуй так давайте для белгородского
only serious questions for the Belgorod grandfather
деда вопросы только
now Booth
серьёзные сейчас Бут Да
Yes, they ask the maestro if you respect
так маэстра спрашивают уважаете ли вы
Moldova That I respect
Молдову Что уважаю
Moldova  of course
Молдову конечно
so uh Anatoly gel asks What is
так ээ Анатолий гель спрашивает Какая у
your
вас
pension normal and the world Hut war to
пенсия нормально а мир Хижина война
palaces asks where you get such
дворцам спрашивает где вы берёте такие
news about these
новости про эти
boilers
котлы
Lord, well, you don’t know this go to the
Господи ну Вам же это неизвестно зади на
Ministry of Defense website and you’ll see everything
сайт Министерство обороны и всё увидишь
understood So
понял Так
uh Andrey asks where you
ээ Андрей спрашивает где вы сейчас
live now in
живёте в
the temporary temporary detention facility  what p VR TRP This is what is a
ПВР что п вр ПВР Это что такое пункт
temporary
временного
accommodation center I mean you were
размещения В смысле вас
evacuated yes and where did you live before this in the
эвакуировали да а а где жили до этого
Belgorod
Белгородской
region I thought you at home seemed to have the
области Я думал Вы у себя дома вроде
same interior as before that I thought
интерьер такой как и раньше что я думал
you were at home because the
что Вы у себя дома потому что вроде
interior seemed to be the same as before  earlier or not, well, I’m sitting in
интерьер такой как и раньше или нет ну в
the basement,
подвале
squealing Oh, yes, I understood a lot. It’s so interesting,
слю щение Ой да Много
so
понял Интересно так
unexpectedly. I thought that you
неожиданно Я думал что вы из самого
were from Belgorod itself. I said how many times,
Белгорода были я сколько раз говорил
Belgorod region. Well, how many times can you say?
Белгородская область Ну сколько говори
You were somewhere closer to the border, yes. Well,
Это вы где-то ближе к границы были да Ну
yes, but it turns out your house is now  under
да а получается Ваш дом сейчас под
occupation Or under fire Why were they
оккупацией Или под обстрелом Почему
evacuated I don’t even know what happened to him Well,
эвакуировали не знаю даже что с ним Ну а
why were you evacuated because the
почему эвакуировали вас потому что
Ukrainians are shelling
украинцы обстреливают
civilians I understood How far from the borders your
жителям понял А сколько от границ ваш
village or settlement was I didn’t
посёлок или населённый пункт был я Не
measure, well, in my opinion 20 km 20 km is normal
мерил ну по-моему 20 км 20 км нормально
my Ukrainians  so
украинцы мой так
uh What is Transnistria
ээ Что такое Приднестровье спрашивают
people from Moldova ask in your opinion
люди из Молдовы по-вашему
What is Transnistria yes
Что такое Приднестровье да
it is a part of Moldova that was formerly
это во часть Молдавии бывшая
and separated from
а отделилась
Moldova General Swan said Moldova
Молдавии генерал лебедь сказал Молдова
there and Transnistria here General Swan
туда а Приднестровье сюда генерал лебедь
is Russian what difference does he have to
- это русский какая ему разница к
Moldova how could he say He said
Молдове как это он мог сказать Он сказал
no  war, whoever shoots says at least
никакой войны кто стрельнет говорит хоть
from a slingshot the spelled
из рогатки полбу
will get
получит
peace asks who is to blame that Belgorod
мир спрашивает кто виноват что Белгород
is being bombed by
бомбят
some,
какие-то
I can’t even say for sure U Well, who is
так я даже зна сказать не могу У Ну кто
bombing it Well, not who is to blame, it’s
его бомбит Ну не а кто виноват то что
clear that Ukraine is bombing, but who is to blame for
бомбит Украина понятно а кто виноват в
the fact that Belgorod is bombing A  what a Peaceful
том что Белгород бомбит А какая Мирный
city Why bomb Who is to blame when the
город Зачем бомбить Кто виноват когда
Peaceful city is bombed I understand and who is
Мирный город бомбят понял а а кто кто
to blame when aerial bombs are dropped on Kharkov
виноват когда на Харьков скидывают
What is on Kharkov Who is
авиационные бомбы что на Харьков Кто
to blame When Russia drops
виноват Когда Россия скидывает на
aerial bombs on Kharkov So where does it
харьковы авиационные бомбы Так куда она
drop what plant the center of Kharkov is
скидывает накой завод центр Харькова
dropped
скидывают
Well, I’m talking about a tank factory  throws off
Ну я говорю на танковый завод скидывает
Well, yes I understand I understand from the instructions I understand Yes
Ну да понял Понял по установкам понял Да
so we went to Kharkov to Barabashov writes
так ездили в Харьков на Барабашова пишет
Vladimir
Владимир
of course
конечно
so who is guarding your house where you
так кто охраняет Ваш дом там где вы
left like
выехали как
[music]
[музыка]
Oh
О
well well they are guarding in short oh I completely forgot Well
ну ну охраняют короче о совсем забыл Ну
who is it the authorities or is there a community There is no
кто это власти или там община Какая нет
National Guard National Guard  I understood And how many
росгвардия росгвардия понял А сколько в
people lived in your locality
вашем населённом пункте человек
I didn’t count Well, that’s 100 200,000 And
жило вот не считал Ну это 100 200.000 А
5,000 how big it was No,
5.000 сколько он большой был Да нет
700 people lived 700 Cool Yes,
человек 700 то жило 700 Прикольно Да
that is, it turns out, look, it
так то есть получается смотрите
turns out that you can say that the war
получается что можно сказать что война
came to your
пришла к вам
home Well, that’s cool Better  If only the Ukrainians would
домой Ну да прикольно Лучше бы украинцы
n’t come in now, they’d be able to tear their legs
не заходили им сейчас быстрее драть ноги
from there faster, and so on. But they don’t
оттуда быстрее а тож так Так они же не
come in, they just fire at
заходят они обстреливают просто из
your house from Ukraine and everything works out,
Украины Ваш дом и всё получается
so I’m asking here, is it possible to say that
так спрашиваю тут можно ли сказать что
your house is in a cauldron or is this
ваш дом в котле находится или это
incorrect? In which cauldron, that is?  he’s not in
некорректно В каком котле то есть его не
trouble, he’s not in a cauldron, he’s just
зах он не в котле его просто
being shelled, so it turns out this is a
обстреливают так получается это
front-line zone, I understand, I understand,
прифронтовая зона понял понял
Igor asks why you’re not fighting, you’re not
так Игорь спрашивает почему не воюете не
defending your
защищаете свои
homes. Well, what can I say to Igor
дома Ну что я могу Игорю
[music]
[музыка]
simply? It’s just not clear why some
просто Просто непонятно почему какой-то
Chechen should defend your home, so this
чеченец должен защищать Ваш дом так это
Russia defends Cheche I understand And you don’t
Россия по чече защищает понял А а вы не
defend you are Russian You’re not for Yes I’m already
защищаете вы русски Вы не заа Да мне уже
73 years old Why should I
73 года Какой мне
start something shorter in chatroulette you sit
пуска что-то короче в чатрулетке сидите
every day I didn’t understand so the
каждый день не понял так
question is can it be that now
вопрос может ли такое быть что сейчас
someone from the National Guard or Akhmat lives
кто-то из росгвардии или Ахмата живёт
now in your
сейчас в вашем
house it is quite possible yes about Rom kis
доме вполне возможно да о Ром кис
asks an interesting question why
спрашивает интересный вопрос почему
defeated Germany lives better than
побеждён ная Германия живёт лучше
the winners of Russia in the Soviet
Победителей России по советские
countries And who said that the
страны А кто сказал что лучше
tricky
хитрый
answer is better yes Ruslan asks Or are you from the
ответ да Руслан спрашивает Или вы из
village of
посёлка
Palatovo that village and Ruslan asks
палатово что посёлка и Руслан спрашивает
Or are you from Well, you live  in the village of
Или вы родом Ну вы живёте в посёлке
Palatovo I heard this for the first time. I also heard Ruslan for the
палатово первый раз слышу Я тоже Руслан
first time. Yes, Rustam
первый раз такое слышу Да Рустам
asks do you have a photo of
спрашивает у вас есть фото
Putin, no, so they ask here. How
Путина не нету так тут спрашивают А как
long ago were you moved? The
давно вас переместили эвакуировали пункт
temporary
временного
accommodation center was evacuated at the end of August this year, yes,
размещения в конце августа этого года да
two on the fourth. Well, naturally, that is,
два четвёртого Ну естественно то есть
already 3 months  it turns out to be about
уже 3 месяца получается где-то
2 and a half cool so
да 2 с половина прикольно так
uh so so
ээ так так
so Irina asks don’t worry that
так Ирина спрашивает не переживайте что
your house could have already taken out everything valuable from
уже ваш дом могли вынести всё ценное из
it that
него что
they could talk about looting and steal
что могли про мародёрство и обворовать
your house from the Russian Guard I think no, well
Ваш дом росгвардия думаю что нет ну
there are videos of Ukrainian heroes dragging everything
ролики есть украинские герои тащат всё
like that  the Ukrainian hero of yours there
подряд так украинский герой ваш там
is guarded by the National Guard and not by the Ukrainian
росгвардия охраняет а не украинские
Hero Nene not our Rova I
Герой нене не нашей Рова Здесь всё
understood everything fine here Yes so well
нормально понял Да
so Welcome to asks how
так Welcome to спрашивает как у вас так
you get information that is unpleasant for you
выходит что неприятную вам информацию
that Russia is bombing the world you are trying as hard as possible
что Россия бомбит мирк вы максимально
that Russia is bombing that Russia is bombing
что Россия бомбит что Россия бомбит
civilians  Kharkov Odessa Kiev that
мирных жителей Харькова Одессы Киева что
you are trying to justify this denier
вы пытаетесь это отрицатель
Well, who is bombing the world, bombing
оправдывать Ну кто бомбит мир бомбят
factories, repair shops, concentrations of
заводы ремонтные мастерские скопления
troops This is a Bomb Yes, with aerial
войск Вот это Бомб Да авиационными
bombs in the city center
бомбами в центре города
Yes, I
Да так
understand what is better, the FSB or the
понял что лучше ФСБ или
Gestapo, stupid question Let’s
гестапо дурацкий вопрос Давай дальше
understand further So
понял Так
uh Elena Mostovaya asks What is the connection
ээ Елена Мостовая спрашивает Какая связь
between yours  the current situation and the
между вашим теперешний положением и
beginning of a special military operation, that
началом специальной военной операции то
is, is your situation a result of the
есть Есть ли ваше положение результатом
beginning of a military
начала военной
operation, I didn’t catch it, let’s say uh If there
операции не уловил скажем ээ Если бы не
had been no special military operation, you would
было специальной военной операции вы бы
now be living quietly in your village,
сейчас спокойно жили в своём посёлке так
yes, that is, it turns out that a special
да то есть получается специальная
operation has nothing to do with it if the
операция здесь не при чём если бы
Ukrainians  the heroes didn’t go to the course,
украинские герои не пошли в курс было
everything was fine Yeah, I understand, that is, yes, that
всё нормально Ага понял то есть да то
is, it’s your fault that you are now at the
есть виноват в том что вы сейчас в
point, the question is why did they go there,
пункте разме вопрос зачем они туда зашли
they’ll beat them already, half of them beat them,
их же побьют уже половина побили их
they’ll finish them off soon, it’s better than leaving there, I
добьют скоро лучше чем уходить оттуда
understand So uh Well, by the way, the
понял Так ээ Так кстати поступила
military received information  They say we don’t have
информация военные говорят у нас нет
an order If there was an order, they would have
приказа Если был бы приказ уже давно бы
finished all this a long time ago, and that is,
всё это закончили а то есть украинца не
Putin is not giving the Ukrainians the order to destroy the Ukrainian
даёт Путин приказ уничтожить украинские
troops,
войска приказа
there is no order for a long time, the Armed Forces were finished, that is, they would have been
нет давно ВС закончили то есть и кие бы
taken in 2 days if there was an order, they would have been
взяли за 2 дня если приказ был что взяли
taken if they had given the order  cues They would have taken it in
ки если бы дали приказ кии Взяли бы за
2 days even yes Well, you hear Well, what does it have to do with here
2-т дня даже да Ну ты слыша Ну причём
[music]
[музыка]
ki and who doesn’t specifically give an order to
ки а кто не даёт специально приказ
liberate the Kursk region Well, probably
освободить курскую область Ну наверно
whoever doesn’t gives it doesn’t give And
кто не даёт тот и не даёт А
why not Damn so Okay, I can only
почему недо Блин так Ладно я могу только
express my opinion
свою высказать
Let’s  Ukrainian troops arrive in the
Давайте украинские войска поступают в
Kursk region they constantly
курскую область поступают постоянно
arrive they arrive and they do
поступают поступают поступают а обратно
n’t
не
come back Yeah, they don’t come back so that’s why maybe
Ага обратно не так что вот поэтому может
I didn’t understand that I understood that is why
не поэто понял понял то есть Поэтому
Putin doesn’t give the order to destroy the
Путин не даёт приказ уничтожить
Ukrainian troops it’s interesting and cool
украинские войска интересно да прикольно
that way If you have a son or grandson Well, he’s already a
так Ели у вас сын или внук Ну уже
very adult  in the war
взрослый очень на войне
I said very adults Well, that’s right,
Я сказал очень взрослые Ну правильно
so much so that if you are 70 then they
настолько что если Вам 70 то им как раз
can just fight what what how old are your grandson and
могут воевать что что сколько внуку и
son Well, this is personal information I
сыну лет Ну это личная информация
understand
понял
So do you consider the
Так считаете ли вы братьями
North Korean
северокорейских
[music]
[музыка]
mercenaries to be brothers Yes,
наёмников Да счита
seriously,
серьёзно
Of course it’s
Конечно
cool like that in the past year  The Soviet Union
прикольно так в птм году Советский Союз
fought for them with America,
же воевал за них с Америкой
now they are brothers, I understand. What do
воевал теперь то они братушки я понял А
you think: Where do people live better in South Korea or North Korea? Well, to know you need to live in both places, as I can say, I understand. What do you think? Where do people live better in
Вы считаете Где лучше живут люди в
Moscow or in Africa I do
Москве или в Африке
n’t know, in Africa no yes Well, you’re
не не знаю в Африке нету да Ну вы полым
completely lost, you understand that in Moscow it’s better
нулись вы понимаете что в Москве лучше
than in Africa Yes, and in Korea it’s so good
чем в Африке Да так и с Корея так хорошо
uh So you personally trained the Koreans already the
ээ Так вы бачили лично корейцев уже
North Koreans
северных корейцев
No, they are already in the Belgorod region
Нет они уже есть в Белгородской области
How can I  say yes I saw Well, maybe
Как я могу сказать есть Видел Ну может
they know yes And why were the Koreans brought to the
знают да А зачем корейцев привезли в
Kursk region that Well Why Russia can’t
курскую область что Ну Почему Россия не
cope without the Koreans And who
может без корейцев справиться А кто
said that it can’t Why did they bring them in then You can’t spoil the porridge
сказал что не может А зачем их тогда
with butter, I understand
притащили Кашу маслом не испортишь понял
yes You can’t spoil Masha with your finger,
да Машу пальцем не испортишь
so tell me
так а вот скажи-ка
why did the Americans go to Bryansk because they
зачем в Брянск американцы полезли потому
can afford it? It’s
что могут себе позволить им это
interesting to them. But what are you asking
интересно А вот что ты спрашиваешь
the Koreans? What are the Americans? Why did
корейцы гово американцы Зачем в Брянск
they go to Bryansk? Who are they? Mercenaries? Who are they?
Пошли они Кто Наёмники они Кто они
freedom residents of a free country can
свобод жители свободной страны могут
do what they want for themselves, and that is, you can,
делать что хочешь себе а то есть и можно
well, to Russia, yes  You can enter Russia
да ну в Россию да в Россию можно входить
because Russia
потому что Россия -
is understandable. So they can. But the Koreans
это понятно Значит им можно А корейцам
are not allowed, the Koreans are
нельзя корейцам
not allowed to do everything
нельзя всё всё
clearly so so so
чётко
so question from Anzhelka
так так так так во вопрос от Анжелка
Why don’t your children and grandchildren
Почему вну дети и внуки не
fight for your
воюют за вашу
homeland, we all fight, but we all
родину у нас все воюют ко нужно все
fight, but you  ask a question
воюют а вот ты задай вопрос
Wow, your house is under occupation, or rather, it’s
Ух Ваш дом в оккупации точнее так
being shelled like this and so on, why is
обстреливает и так дальше почему вот ваш
n’t yours being protected? Do you support yours so that
не идёт защи вы поддерживаете сво чтобы
someone else will die for you and the forest to
за вас умирал кто-то другой и лес на
Ukraine? Yes, I’m 73 years old. Well, children, grandchildren,
Украину Да мне 73 года Ну а дети внуки
okay, that’s okay.  Nya
ладно так воз Окей окей ме вки девоч ня
girls girls such ichni inci
девочки девочки такое ични инци
Use asks Sergey
Пользуйтесь спрашивает Сергей
Ralko what other sources are you
ралько ещё какими источниками ну где вы
in some Telegram channel on TV
в каком-то Telegram канале в телевизоре
Where do you get information from Telegram
Где вы берёте информацию в Telegram
channels And what Telegram channels are these
каналах А какие Telegram каналы это
media understood Interesting so let’s move on uh
СМИ понял Интересно так едем дальше ээ
Is there democracy in North Korea How
Есть ли демократия в Северной Корее Как
you think
вы считаете
I’m asking, I wasn’t there, I don’t
спрашивать я я же я же там не был не
know why the Soviet army
понял зачем Советская армия в сорок
marched into the territory of
пятом году шла на территорию
Hitler’s
гитлеровской
Germany in 1945, why did the Soviet army
Германии что зачем Советская армия в
invade the territory of
1945 году вторглась на территорию
Hitler’s Germany in 1945, and who is asking this question?
гитлеровской Германии а кто этот вопрос
Who is asking this question? Now I’ll
задаёт Кто этот вопрос задаёт сейчас
tell you how  he is so where is
скажу как он так где
he now
он сечас сейчас
now now Elena Mostovaya
сейчас Елена Мостовая
I
Я прошу
apologize since you can’t say that to a woman like
прощения раз нельзя так женщине говорить
that I understand I’m speaking mildly The
вы что я понимаю я мягко говорю
Soviet army entered Germany in 1945
Советская армия в сорок пятом году вошла
Well yes yes yes So make a note
в Германию Ну да да да Так вот заметку
on the stupid one, Germany was already defeated in 1945
сделайте на глупенькая в со ПМ году уже
Well, this is because
Германию разбили Ну так это потому что в
what did the allies come in with? The
со чем зашли союзники в со
Americans were defeated in the presence of the
че Американ разбили в при
troops for the parade, come in to take
войска для парада зайти
a photo. So okay, let's move
сфотографироваться Так ладно едем
on to the question. Do you have this
далее вопрос У вас вы у вас есть этот
grandfather on a stick there when this Immortal
дед на палке там когда этот Бессмертный
Regiment is definitely there, definitely is, I
полк обязательно есть обязательно есть
understand
понял
So
Так
yeah Welcome  to UK they ask when the
угу Welcome to UK спрашивают когда
Armed Forces of Ukraine were advancing in the
Вооружённые силы Украины наступали в
Kharkov region, you said the
Харьковской области вы говорили то же
same thing as in the SRF, thus driving
самое что в срф таким образом загоняли
everyone into a trap, you still believe in it
всу в ловушку вы до сих пор в это верите
again. Well, when Ukraine was advancing in the
ещё раз Ну что когда Украина наступала в
Kharkov region and drove away
Харьковской области и прогонял
Russian troops. What are you all about?  they also
российские войска Да что ваши все также
said that it is the Ukrainians who are being lured into
говорили что это украинцев заманивают в
a trap, I don’t know anything about it, okay,
ловушку ничего не знаю про это ладно
so Elena says that girls at the front
Так Елена говорит что девочки на фронте
in the Russian army are very needed, especially
в русской армии очень нужны особенно
Natasha, something she meant, I don’t know,
Наташе что-то она имела в виду не знаю
maybe she works in medicine, so according to the IFR,
может медициной работает так вот по ифр
women began to be drafted into the army  Yes, I'm
женщин начали забирать в армию Да я
watching You know about us so
смотр Вы про нас знаете так
question Why are you always in the same clothes
вопрос Почему вы всегда в одной одежде
Dory Dory asks I really like it, I
Дори дори спрашивает Мне так нравится
understand why Mercedes are not asking
понял шда Мерседесов на спрашивают
Solovyov, look what what Solovyov
Соловьёва смотрите что что Соловьёва
look I don’t sleep under it, I turn
смотрите Не я под него сплю я включаю
it on and sleep peacefully under it One mow my
его и спокойно под него сплю Един кось
claw
когте
[music  ]
[музыка]
interest writes that you are a military pensioner And an
интерес пишет что вы военный пенсионер И
FSB officer no, he is a music teacher olas
фсбшник нет он преподаватель музыки олас
he is a teacher He has long been
он преподаватель Он давно
identified as when Oleg Vaida
идентифицирован так когда вам Олег вайда
asks you when it was better for you to live
спрашивает когда вам лучше жить было
now or 3 years
сейчас или 3 года
ago Yes, the same Same I understood,
назад Да одинаково Одинаково понял не
life has not changed yes, not well now well
изменилось жизнь да а не ну сейчас ну
now pensions  increased salaries
сейчас пенсии прибавили зарплаты
increased in this regard better Yeah, you
прибавили в этом отношении лучше Угу в
’re sitting in the basements, yes,
подвалах сидите да
because you belong to the Russian
так как относитесь к русскому
volunteer corps. And
добровольческому корпусу
I saw him, I met him, well,
А я что видел его встречался с ним ну
these are those who fight against Russia and the
это те которые воюют против России и
Russians. And where are they fighting in the Kursk
русские А где Они воюют в Курской
region in the Belgorod region there
области в Белгородской области пленных
were no prisoners and  they don’t surrender to captivity They
не было а они в плен не сдаются Они же
know the Russians Yes they are Russian Russians don’t
русские знают Да они русские русские не
surrender
сдаются
like that Okay next uh
так Окей дальше
Rustan asks or do you play
ээ спрашивает Рустан или вы занимаетесь
sports
спортом
I understand Pavel Otaman
твою занимаюсь понял Павел отаман
asks Or are these
спрашивает Или это
glasses? He says to his wife that these are women’s
очки У жены он говорит что это женские
glasses yes or
очки да или
no Or
нет Или
yours I just don’t  I know I’m not an
ваши Я просто не знаю я не
ophthalmologist Let’s move on Otherwise I understand Vyru far away Do
окулист Давай дальше А то се Выру даль
n’t If you want to swear,
понял Не Если хотите ругаться ругайтесь
swear I don’t swear God I understand so
Я не ругаюсь Боже понял так
where did you vacation abroad asks Ani
где за границей отдыхали спрашивает Ани
Yangol Turkey Egypt and Greece I understand and for the
янгол Турция Египет и Греция понял а
last 3 years Where did you vacation Turkey and
последние 3 года Где отдыхали Турция а
not Turkey yes In what
не Турция да В каком
year Yes  I don’t remember anymore, well, after we started,
году Да я уже не помню ну после начала
we were on vacation abroad. No, that’s what I
сво отдыхали за границей Не ну вот это я
asked, yes, life has become better.
и спрашивал да да жизнь стала лучше
Andre asks, watch football, no, I
Андре спрашивает смотрите футбол нет
understand how our famous comedian Raikin
понял как у нас известный комик Райкин
said, 22
говорил 22
bulls, yes, if they dug such a hole, what
бугая да если они такую яму выкопали Что
did I understand, Natalya, saving, asks why  you
понял Наталья спаская спрашивает почему
don’t want to listen to
не хотите слушать
acordi, so you understand how I do, it’s not that I do
акорди так понимаете как я не то что его
n’t want to listen to him, if he was playing, I
не хочу слушать если бы он играл был я
listened to him, and they also play the disc for him There
его слушал а тоже за него играт диск Там
Ore’s game started playing, he really plays
Оре игра его заиграло он реально играет
otd and started playing, he showed it, and again I’m
отд и заиграй он отсл показал и опять я
not saying that, friend  won’t work Yes, he
говорю не друг так не пойдёт Да он
really plays, I don’t know him that way, why is
реально играет я его знаю не так а чем
he then afraid to show off from the camera
он тогда боится отсе от камеры показать
that he’s playing? In short, okay, I don’t understand
что он играет Короче ладно я не понимаю
what’s going
что
on Rom RM asks how you feel
так Ром РМ спрашивает как вы относитесь
about Russian terrorists in Africa, what kind of
к российским террористам в Африке каким
grandmother in Africa does the Russian
бабке в Африке к российским террористам
Wagnerian terrorists in  How do we relate to Africa and that in
вагнеровцам в Африке как относи а что в
Africa there are terrorists and Wagnerites,
Африке террористы есть да вагнеровцы
but I just don’t understand how you feel about
да никак понял как вы относитесь к
Nemtsov, who doesn’t care about
немцову кому к
Nemtsov
немцову
in any way
никак
So why did Stalin attack Finland
Так зачем Сталин напал на Финляндию
asks Ajey
спрашивает аджей
and Finland was told you are given
а Финляндии было сказано вам отдаётся
Karelia,
Карелия
we are moving the border 150 km they did not
мы ото двигаем границу на 150 км они не
agree so it began  Finnish
согласились поэтому началась финская
war now The Ovit border is 150
война сейчас Граница овита на 150
km from this time Vasil asks what
км с этим поря Василь спрашивает что
will you do if your house is settled by
будете делать если ваш дом заселят
refugees from the Kherson region
беженцев с Херсонской области
supporting
поддерживающих
Russia Which house is your
России Какой дом ваш
house
дом
or in the Mausoleum asks Yaropolk 986 he
вы или в Мавзолее спрашивает ярополк 986
was nearby many times but didn’t get in at all
рядом много раз был но никак не попал
very scary was not not  I got it, I got it, it’s scary.
очень страшный была не не попал понял
I mean, there’s a big line there, a
страшно В смысле что очередь большая там
hundred, and the line is scary, I’m very scared,
сто а очередь страшно мне очень страшно
yes, that is, people stand for hours
да то есть это ещё люди стоят часами
to look at Lenin, it’s hard, of course,
чтобы посмотреть на Ленин жесть конечно
so,
так
uh, you’re listening to the Shaman, he’s asking, Well, it
ээ Шамана слушаешь спрашивает Ну мне
’s enough for me that I hear him in the media,
достаточно что я в СМИ слышу его то
so have you watched the interview?  Prigozhin
так смотрели ли вы интервью пригожина
where He told How it started This is
где Он рассказал С чего начали Это
madness in what year and who
безумие в чем году и кто
stole the interview Prigozhin where
разворовали ли вы интервью пригожина где
He told How it all started Vche I
Он рассказал С чего началось всё это
understood who killed
понял кто убил
Prigozhin How to say
пригожина Как сказать
the head of the Chevy
руководитель чевы
so he was already the head of the PMC what What
так он уже был руководитель чвк что Что
Who killed Prigozhin And who  killed Well,
кто убил пригожина А кто убил Ну
questions How can I know, well, your
вопросы Откуда же я могу знать ну ваши
assumptions Yes, I
предположения Да даже предполагать
don’t even want to make scary assumptions Yes, conclusions
нехочу страшно предположить Да выводы
should be drawn yes And I also want to
нужно бы делать да А ещё хочется домой
go home so the decor asks when it
вернуться так декор спрашивает когда
will end in your opinion
закончится сво по-вашему
Well,
Ну и
[music]
[музыка]
questions like that Okay, I would like it to be
вопросы так Окей хотелось бы чтобы
understood quickly  where they did their military
скорей понял где проходили срочную
service in the infantry Well, geographically,
службу в пехоте Ну а территориально
where Transbaikalia understood
где Забайкалья понял
Tin
Оловянная
Dada Yeah
Дада Ага
lead
свинцовая
so so so so how old are you and
так так так так сколько вам лет а
said 70 plus
говорил 70 плюс
Yes,
Да
will you cry when Putin
так будете ли плакать когда Путин
dies I think no I understand er New
умрёт думаю что нет понял э р New
ask Trump or
спрашивают Трамп или
Harris Trump understand PZ asks  what
Харрис Трамп понял ПЗ спрашивает что
unites a Tuvinian and a Muscovite on the same
объединяет тувинца и Москвича на одной
territory? A Muscovite
территории
and a Tuvinian from
Москвича и кого и тувинца из
Tuva, the territory of
Тувы територия
Rodina Russia. Well, what do they have a common
Родина Россия Ну что что у них обще
cultural code?
культурный код что зачем ем быть в одном
- How why was he
странные вопросы какие-то Как зачем
born, he added such happiness, he was born
родился вот счастье такое подлил родился
in Russia, well, Okay Prestige asks in
в России ну О'кей Престиж спрашивает в
1917 who would you be for the Reds or the
1917 за кого бы были за красных или
Whites of course for the Reds for the Reds
белых конечно за красных за красных
so if you served in Transbaikalia about the
так так если вы служили в Забайкалье про
threat from China
угрозу от Китая
and when should you ask  this
а когда это надо спросить у этого
comrade, when the threat began I don’t know,
товарища когда угроза началась Я не знаю
but the question is strange, of course, it
так вот вопрос-то странный конечно напря
was tense when Damansky Island was here, it
был когда Остров Даманский был тут
was tense, yes, he asks what
напряг был да шда спрашивает что
happened to
случилось с
Navalny, a person died, well, it happens
Навальным умер человек ну случается
that a person dies. I
такое что человек умирает
understand Maxim asks an interesting
Понял Максим спрашивает интересный
question: should Putin be put in the
вопрос надо ли Путина положить в
Mausoleum  like
Мавзолей как
Lenin Let's
Ленина Давай дальше
understand further yuvis yuvis Asks you will return
понял ювис ювис Спрашивает Вы вернётесь
home if he ends up in Ukraine That is,
домой если он окажется в Украине То есть
if, as a result of the agreements, your
если по результатам договорённостей ваша
territory goes to Ukraine If I
территория отойдёт к Украине Если
return if your village in the Belgorod
верну если ваш посёлок Белгородской
region goes to Ukraine Yes, you will return
области отойдёт Украине Да вы вернётесь
home there Yes God SBA
туда домой Да Боже СБА
God what do I need yours there  country do
Боже что же мне там вашей стране делать
understood asks how do you feel about
понял спрашивает р как относитесь к
migrants from Kazakhstan Kyrgyzstan
мигрантам из Казахстана Кыргызстана
Uzbekistan
Узбекистана
Tajikistan Well, people are different migrants
Таджикистана Ну люди разные мигранты
there are disgusting migrants they are
есть есть отвратительные мигранты их
expelled there People are normal in different ways Uh-
высылают есть Люди нормальные по-разному
huh emli asks how in Russia they
Угу эмли спрашивает как в России
help people with
помогают лю людям с
disabilities well you know quite
инвалидностью ну вы знаете достаточно
well
хорошо
[music]
[музыка]
they help  how specifically
помогают как конкретно
financially the means of rehabilitation are
материально средства реабилитации
quite good And how many pensions are there
достаточно хорошо А сколько пенсий
now in Russia,
сейчас в России
so look at who has 60 And who has
так смотри а у кого У кого и 60 А у кого
15 and who has 60
и 15 у кого 60
Interesting, I understood from the veterans of the Armed Forces,
Интересно у ветеранов Вооружённых Сил
but from the rest, I understood all 15, so
понял а у остальных всех 15 понял так
the question Konstantin is interesting Why did they
вопрос Константин интересный Почему за
fight for Damansky  and then they
Даманский воевали а потом добровольно
gave it up voluntarily And who said that they
отдали А кто сказал что добровольно
gave it up voluntarily And what they forcibly gave up
отдали А что принудительно отдали
This is a question to ask what
Это вопрос зат спросить что такое Остров
Damansky Island is, what is it Konstantin What
Даманский что это такое Константин Что
is
такое Остров
Damansky Island, answer This is a river flowing full of sand
Даманский отве Это река течёт нала песка
It was Oman, the river washed away the sand and
Это был Оман река смыла песок и никакого
there is no island so what else  they didn’t give him away, it’s
острова нет так что а то его не отдали
just that the river washed away everything on the island and it
просто река смыла острове всё и
will end, of course, he was never there,
закончится ко конечно его как не было
so Stick understands. He asks what is the disadvantage of your left eye. He’s probably an ophthalmologist. Let him ask his grandmother. I understand. So Rustam asks Bush’s legs in the nineties, did
понял Так Рустам спрашивает в девяностых
you eat
ножки Буша вы
the question, how did you eat?
кушали же вопрос ещё как кушал понял
Bartholomew is asked for cabbage soup or borscht, what did you
Варфоломей спрашивают щи или борщ что вы
choose? I
выбрали
love both
люблю
so
так
fre asks an interesting question Why are
фре спрашивает интересный вопрос Почему
you in the basement at a temporary
вы в подвале в пункте временного
accommodation center and not at your
размещения а не у своих
children Anya? Where are Anya at her children’s
детей Ани Они где Ани у своих детей
house? So at my house where we were
дома Так а у меня дома где мы же
evacuated? Which one?  And the children were also
эвакуированы какой А дети тоже
evacuated. Well, of course. I thought I was
эвакуированы Ну а как же А я думал я
evacuated with the children left. I didn’t think
эвакуировал с дети остались не я думал
that your children were already living there in Belgorod
что ваши дети живут уже там в Белгороде
or Moscow, but they were in the same place. And your
или в Москве а они в том же А ваши
adult children, too, go to temporary
взрослые дети тоже подь временном
accommodation, what are you doing, your children are adults?
размещения что дела ваши дети взрослые
Yes, and  grandchildren, they are now also in a
Да и внуки они сейчас тоже в пункте
temporary
временном
accommodation center. Well, of course it’s
размещения Ну конечно
screwed up,
капец
and how many of you are there as a whole family, like this
так и сколько вас там всей семьи вот так
now in a temporary accommodation center
сейчас в пункте временного размещения
since
уже с
August? What, how many members of your
августа сколько Что сколько членов вашей
family are living there like this in a temporary accommodation center?
семьи вот так в пункте временного
Let’s skip the question, let’s skip it.
живёт Давайте пропустим вопрос пропустим
Yes, they’re just people  they think that after all, your
Да просто люди думают что всё-таки ваши
children are not in a temporary accommodation center, they
дети не в пункте временного размещения
don’t believe
не верят
so Lily asks how you see
так Лили спрашивает как вы видите
the end of yours, how it should
окончание сво чем вот она должна
end
закончиться
like Well, there’s nothing to even think about here, either the surrender
как Ну тут даже и думать нечего тут либо
of
капитуляция
Ukraine or a military military Victory
Украины либо военной военная Победа
of Russia Well, surrender is a
России Ну так капитуляция это есть
military Victory  yes The question is, how do you see
военная Победа да Вопрос как вы видите
this?
это
Well, that’s what should force Ukraine to
Ну вот что должно принудить Украину к
capitulate.
капитуляции Да
Yes, the last negotiations in Turkey
вот переговоры последни в в Турции
broke down. Zelensky said we won’t
сорвались Зеленский сказал не будем
talk about it, but the negotiations were about what, so as not to
перего а переговоры были О чём чтобы не
hit those on the central
бить по те по центральном по
electricity supply, and he disrupted all this, here
электроэнергии а он сорвал всё это вот
you go  yes, yes, it turns out that what
те и пожалуйста да да то получается что
needs to be done for Ukraine to surrender, what
нужно сделать чтобы Украина сдалась что
that Russia must, we haven’t given up for the
что Россия должна вот мы не сдаёмся уже
third year already, to win, but
третий год победить а
how are we starting from Mariupol, Sva
ну как как вот начинаем С Мариуполя Сва
Well, Victory, capture everything, capture Kiev, capture
Ну Победа всё захватить Киев захватить
Lvov, where is the final measure of
Львов где конечное мерило
Victory, we will reach at least the Dnieper and there it
Победы дойдём хотя бы до Днепра а там
will be  view and Okay you will see well
будет вид а О'кей будете видеть хорошо
so
так
so Kruka asks Is it possible in your
так крука спрашивает Можно ли по вашему
opinion for Russia to end its tomorrow
мнению Россия закончить своего завтра
or
или
not some fools I don’t know stupid
нет какие-то дурачки не знаю глупый
question Well, it seems to me that it’s possible Putin
вопрос Ну а и мне кажется можно Путин
signs a decree on the end of his All of mine is
подписывает указ о окончании свой Всё я
over Yeah
закончилось Ага
now it’s like that  until Russia achieves
сейчас так пока с Россия не достигнет
its goals, sign nothing, so from
своих целей ничего подписываться так со
your own, you only dream of
своих вы вы там мечтаете только до
reaching the Dnieper. I’m with And there you
Днепра дойти Я с А там уже дальше ничего
don’t see anything further and no goals. Well, when we get there,
не видите и целей Ну вот как дойдём
then we’ll see, I understand Ani Yangol
тогда будет видно понял Ани янгол
asks if there are relatives in
спрашивает есть родственники в
Ukraine, Lord, he’s already been like this  question
Украине Господи уже был такой вопрос Нет
No no so
нету так
so Inna asks Your son is in
так Инна спрашивает Ваш сын в
Germany not in
Германии нет в
[music]
[музыка]
Russia
России
so in Mariupol they
так в Мариуполе
were No I didn’t understand but we went to Crimea
были Нет не был понял а в Крым ездили
to rest after ours Where to Crimea to Crimea
отдыхать после сво Куда в Крым в Крым
after ours Well of course like
после сво Ну конечно как
after this year after I already I  already
после в этом году после Я уже я уже
now I don’t
сейчас никуда не
understand anywhere Tatyana Tatyana writes interestingly
понял Татьяна Татьяна пишет интересно
She wants wine for you to get ready normal
Она вино хочет вас подк гот нормальные
goals of yours now you live in the
цели сво теперь Вы живёте в
basement in
подвале в
[music]
[музыка]
as a result of Swa how do you feel about the exchange Denis
результате Сва как относитесь к обм Дени
and who fired at them in trouble grandfather fact
а кто их обстреливал в бе деде факто
Russia You see everything That is, when Belgrade
росия Всё видишь То есть когда Белград
is  it means Ukraine is shelling And when
это значит Украина обстреливает А когда
Russia it means either at factories or
Россия это значит либо по заводам либо
Where is the fact who is
Где где факт курскую область кто
shelling the Kursk region Ukraine Ukraine Yes Ukraine is
обстреливает Украина Украина Да курскую
shelling the Kursk region
область обстреливает Украина
Yes Ukraine is shelling the Kursk region
Да Украина обстреливает курскую область
and Belgorod is not Ukraine Ukraine
а Белгород не Украина Украина
is shelling Belgorod Yes Ukraine is also not the
обстреливает Белгород Да Украина тож не
Koreans shelling Belgorod Ukraine
корейцы обстреливает Белгород Украина
is shelling the Kursk region  Yes
обстреливает и курскую область да
Yes Absolutely true Yes, like in the gas sector
Да Абсолютно верно Да как в секторе газа
Yes Absolutely
да Абсолютно
true In short, yes in Belgorod the course
верно короче да по Белгороду курс
would reach Moscow and in Moscow that’s
доставали бы до Москвы и по Москве бы
really the question you are Well, you are
это реально вопрос вы ж Ну вы ж вы ж
correct Why don’t you have victories in the
правильный А почему ж у вас побед на
war, but now yes  now
войне нету а по то теперь да то теперь
look, here I am saying, yes, we are hitting the
смотри вот я говорю да мы бьём по
Kursk and Belgorod regions.
Курской и Белгородской области А вы
Why did you hit the Ahmadi children’s hospital?
зачем по детской больнице Ахмади ударили
Yes, where? Name where who is this fact, let’s
Да где Назови где кто это факт давай так
say it like that in 3 years of war, yes,
давай так скажи за 3 года войны да
Russia has never hit civilians,
Россия ни разу не ударила по мирным
no, maybe
нет возможно
only  Let's keep moving on Yes, I got it
только Всё едем дальше Да понял
So
Так
[music]
[музыка]
uh-huh
угу
So you're a Nazi asking redhot
Так вы нацист спрашивает редхот
fool Let's move on f asks aren't
дура Давай дальше ф спрашивает не
you afraid that they will find you after the end of
боитесь что вас найдут после окончания
your mission that after Russia loses a
сво что после того как Россия проиграет
special military operation aren't you afraid
специальное военное операции не боитесь
that they'll
что вас
find you This is who
найдут Это кто
asks What is Finland
спрашивает А что это такое Финляндия на
got it in touch
связи понял
[music]
[музыка]
yeah,
угу
so the question is interesting by the way, all the
так вопрос кстати интересный все военные
Russian military in the Kursk region in the
российские в Курской области в
Belgorod region They live Where in
Белгородской области Они проживают Где в
military units or in some
военных частях или в каких-то
houses Yes, everywhere we have Volunteers and
домах Да везде у нас и Добровольцы и
mobilized from Khabarovsk Vladivostok
мобилизованы из Хабаровска Владивостока
Chelyabinsk Irkutsk everything is correct, that
Челябинска Иркутска всю правильно то
is, not  They now live
есть не Они проживают сейчас получается
in residential buildings, but that’s
в жилых домах та
how they belong to military units,
так они относятся к к воинским частям да
yes, well, yes, well, they live there, there are not so many
да ну да ну живут они там же нет столько
military units for
воинских частей чтобы с казарма чтобы
them to live there from the barracks, yes, they came from all over
они там жили да они приехали со всей
Russia and now they live where
России и сейчас живут где
they are, my questions.  I would like to say:
они мой вопросы Так и хочется сказать Э
Why did the military units come, not to
для воинские части для чего приехали не
live at home, but to fight correctly? Well,
жить по домам а воевать правильно Ну вот
they are tearing off the trenches,
они отрывают окопы
dugouts, fortifications, that’s where they live. They live
блиндажи укрепление вот там они Живут
well, that is, it turns out that they live
хорошо то есть получается вообще живут
only all the time, only in the trenches and
только всё время только в окопах и
dugouts, they don’t use the infrastructure of the
блиндажа не используют инфраструктуру
house there. Wash, and so on.
дома там Помыться и так дальше
spend the night no, you're deceiving,
переночевать нет обманываешь обманываешь
you're deceiving Look, you're deceiving You
Смотри это ты обманываешь Ты точно
know me for sure, my friend's wife says her husband is at
знаешь меня знакомая жена говорит муж
the congress to
съезде
get winter things, he arrived, the chickens,
э зимних вещей набрать он приехал куры
geese are intact, he comes home and our soldiers are sitting there.
гуси цел заходит домой а там сидят наши
He asks what are you, Yes, they've come in,
воины Он спрашивает что вы Да вот зашли
he says, Eat chickens,
пог он гово Ешьте курей
I
я правильно
understand correctly that yours  the military, your military
понимаю что ваши военные ваши военные
enters residential buildings, so the owner gave permission,
заходят в жилые дома так хозяин разрешил
he said
он сказал
yes, I understand correctly that Ukrainian
ре Да я правильно понимаю что украинские
troops can hit these houses because
войска могут бить по этим домам потому
there is a concentration of
что там скопление
military personnel there. What kind of clusters? Well,
военных каких Какие скопления Ну
look, if the Russian military came in,
смотрите если российские военные зашли
let’s find out what is a cluster of
давай выясним Что такое скопление вотт
people, military, this is a cluster of a
человека военных это скопление
cluster  he’s a military man Well, let’s not have a
скопление он военный Ну давай не будем
discussion Let’s even if one military man
дискуссии Давайте даже если один военный
if he came into the house He’s a military man he’s a
если он зашёл в дом Он военный он
target if the owner allowed the military men Yes to
цель если хозяин разрешил военным Да
be at home to eat in short and feeds
быть у себя дома кушать короче и кормит
them Yes, why is he then worried that
их Да ну почему он тогда переживает что
his house was bombed because it’s an arrival
его дом разбомбили потому что прилёт
because  looks there about there military
потому что смотрит там о там военные
boos, okay, this is a conversation for
лупи ладно это разговор для
fools,
дурачков
so yes so yes they ask But if
так так так так да спрашивают А вот если
you have all now left these regions
вы сейчас все уехали из этих регионов
Who feeds the chickens and
Кто там кормит курей и
geese There is no one, they feed themselves Yes,
гусей Да никто они сами кормятся да
as far as I
насколько я
know, near Sudzha, in my opinion, 1,000 were released
знаю под Судже по-моему было выпущено
pig farm and then
1.000 свиней ферму и потом и начали
advertisements immediately began to appear selling
сразу появляться объявления продаём
pork And we received a message not to
свинину А у нас прошло изве сообщение не
buy this pork may be contaminated, it’s
покупать эту свинину может быть заражено
quite possible that not all of the pork was beaten,
вполне возможно свинину побили не всё
of course, but they were beaten, I
конечно но побили
understood. So it’s interesting, yes, with the house
понял Так интересно да с домом
it turns out, you see these that the soldiers are
получается видите эти что солдатики там
warming themselves in the houses they live in  they wash themselves in the houses and
греются в домах живут в домах моются
eat, Yes, well, and then no one lives there in the houses.
едят Да так Ну а потом никто там в домах
Well, you said it yourself. You did
не живёт Так вон вы ж сами сказали Вы
n’t say that I said that they come there,
сказали не я сказал что они приходят там
they eat, they came in. Yes, come in, and then he
едят заходили Да заходи да а потом
flies in. I understood the question well. Well, it’s not like a
прилетает понял хорошо вопрос Ну не то
brigade of 5,000 people came in and lives
что бригада 5.000 человек зашла и живёт
in the houses the
в домах
question is good If five soldiers
вопрос хорошо Если пять человек солдат
entered the house and a drone strike flew into the house,
зашли в дом а и по дому прилетел удар
who is to blame for the fact that this house
дрона кто виноват в том что этот дом
was destroyed so and the Drone They are already bombing that
разрушен так а Дрон Они и так бомбят что
so it’s not not Well, who is to blame for
так что это не не Ну вот кто виноват в
the fact that the Drone flew into that  uh, the house where the
том что Дрон прилетел в тот э дом где
Russian soldiers are sitting
сидят русские
Well, here we have Evgeniy, like
солдаты Ну вот у нас Евгений подобный
our war correspondent, driving near
наш военный корреспондент ехал возле
the house, what happened to him The
дома что с ним случилось
drone determined that he was a military man, so he
Дрон определил что он военный так он
can be seen Yes, he’s a military target, they were
видно Да он ж военная цель это ж его
herding him, so he’s
пасли так ему
turning around why are your military
разворачивает зачем ваши военные
hiding in houses and
прячутся в домах и
[  music] of
[музыка]
the chicken coop Swat Give yours
курятника Сват Дайте свою
from o to
от о до
de Let's move on Let them ask about their women like
де Давай дальше Пускай о свои жинки
this Kruka asks Don't worry
так крука спрашивает Вы не переживайте
that you won't
что из-за вра в ра не
get into heaven because of your lies
попадёте из-за вранья что из-за своего
Don't worry that you won't go to
вранья не переживайте что не попадёте в
heaven because of your lies Well  actually, I don’t believe in
рай Ну вообще-то я не верю в
[music]
[музыка]
it’s not enough, practically no, but Ukraine is
это мало практически нет а вот Украина
yes Oh welcome to ask What is the
то да Ой welc to спрашивают Чем
difference between Goebbels’s propaganda and
отличается Пропаганда геббельса от
Solovyov’s propaganda Come
Соловьева Давай
on,
дальше
who is smarter than Kadyrov or Putin
так кто умнее Кадыров или Путин
[music]
[музыка]
Come
Давай
on, the oil refinery asks why after
дальше НПЗ спрашивает почему после
Why after the announcement  mobilization in
Почему после объявления мобилизации в
Russia, a million citizens left, they are
России миллион граждан уехало это
traitors and there is
предатели и
no homeland. Why did they leave? I heard
нет А почему они уехали я слышал
information about the Great Patriotic War.
информацию Великую Отечественную войну
When the war began.
Когда война началась велико отечествен
there is such a thing. How could such a
такая есть Как из ССР можно такое
huge number of people leave the USSR?
огромное количество было покинуть Так
So, well, where did people go? There weren’t
что что ну куда люди это же не было
planes, how did they leave? So many
самолётов как они вот покинули Столько
people, where did they
людей куда они
go? sha 1/7 of the land is generally on earth,
уехали ша 1/7 часть суши вообще на земле
and so for proof, not in
а чтобы для для доказательства не в
which country are they  left Russia left at
какую страну они уехали из России ушёл в
2:00 a.m. That is, 2 hours before the war So
2:00 ночи То есть за 2 часа до войны Так
how did you feel about Ukrainians before
так как относились вы к украинцам до
2014 Yes, I have a
2014 года Да прекрасно я и сейчас
great
прекрасно
attitude even now How do you feel about being
отношусь Как вы относитесь к тому что
arrested for posters For peace
арестовывают за плакаты За мир
in Russia, what is an arrest like  do you feel about
в России что аресто как вы относитесь к
the fact that in Russia people are arrested for
тому что в России арестовывают за
posters For
плакаты За
peace? And where is someone
мир А где это кого
arrested? This is the first time I’ve heard about this, that
аресто первый раз слышу об этом чтоб в
Zamir was arrested in Russia. Yes, there
России Замир арестовывали Да У этого
is something unrealistic in this person’s brain; there are
человека в мозгах что-то не реально есть
a lot of people coming out with whether we pay for peace or
куча выходят люди с платим за мир или
not to war and
нет войне и
in Russia Look, I
в России Посмотрите Я даже ни одного
don’t even understand a single video like this I understand because you’re
ролика такого не Поня потому что вы
watching something about Ukraine, I understood it
что-то про Украину смотрите понял
like that And an interesting question: Why to
так А во интересный вопрос Почему в
Belgorod? I don’t know why in the Belgorod
Белгород Я не знаю почему в Белгородской
region you can’t keep pigs in private
области нельзя держать свиней в частных
households and what does Lotkov’s complex have to do with it?
домохозяйства и причём тут комплекс
What did anyone say?  that you can’t
лоткова Какие кто сказал что нельзя
keep a pig at home What kind of nonsense
свине дома держать Что за чушь
Well, yes, in principle, in every Russian family,
Ну да в принципе в каждой российской сем
yes, in every Russian family in the
да В каждой российской семье в
Belgorod region there is a pig like a
Белгородской области есть по свинье типа
circle or whatever you are doing so Alex
круг или там что вы так так Алекс
asks who whom do you respect from
спрашивает кого кого вы уважаете из
Ukraine Yes, to be honest
Украины Да честно сказать
[music]
[музыка]
no one  and that there is someone to respect,
никого а что там есть кого уважать
he simply asked And who do you respect from Russia
спросил просто А кого уважаете из России
Where did Poroshe
Куда
go Where did
делся Куда делся
Poroshe go, how did he go and who from
пороше ан как его делся да кого вы из
Russia do you respect agriculture they
России уважаете сельского хозяйства они
lined their pockets Russia do you respect who from Russia do you
карманы набили Росси
respect him I
уважаете кого вы из России уважаете его
will respect Okay from Russia who do you
буду уважать Окей из России кого вы
respect what  it means I respect Mishustin so
уважаете что значит Уважаю мишустина так
Putin
Путина
so I
так
understand everything enough
понял
Irina asks me to tell you from the chat that you are
Ирина просит передать вам от чата что вы
rare And what
редкостный А что
is I don’t know a new term
такое не знаю новый термин
some kind of
какой-то
synonym Well this is an example of
синоним Ну это пример
a synonym Yeah So that
синоним Угу Так
Lucy asks about what action
э та Люся спрашивает про какое действие
in life do
в жизни
you regret Yes I don’t particularly regret anything  about
жалеете Да особо не жалею ни о
which I didn’t do anything bad to anyone,
чём плохого ничего никому не делал так
so I lived for
что мне жить
19 years, went to work like this and worked for 44 years.
19 лет пошл работать так и 44 года
So Sergei asks
отработал Так что Сергей спрашивает
such a rather sensitive question,
такое довольно щепетильный вопрос
do you respect
уважаете ли вы
Kadyrov,
Кадырова
I respect Lisne asks why, with such a
уважаю лисне спрашивает почему при такой
good life in Russia, most people go
хорошей жизни в России большинство едет
from Russia to Europe and the USA  your
из России в Европу и США ваше
opinion that from Russia Why if it’s
мнение что из Росси Почему если в России
so good to live in Russia Why from Russia and the
так хорошо жить Почему из Росси м
USA Well, they always went like this and in the 10th century
США Ну так всегда ездили и в де в X веке
they went and still do. Well, what’s wrong with that?
ездили и сейчас ездят Ну что тут такого
Elena asks if you’re watching
Елена спрашивает смотрите ли вы канал
Zolkin’s channel, who’s
золкина канал кого
Zolkin’s channel and the First LTO Take a look
золкина а Первый лто тако Посмотрите
Vladimir Zolkin is an interesting journalist from
Владимир золкин интересный журналист из
Ukraine,
Украины
what is Ukrainian, he does this with your prisoners with
че украинский он с вашими пленными с
your prisoners interviews,
вашими пленными интервью
asks Neo, or did you
так спрашивает Нео или вы ходили
once go to a
когда-то на концерт
Kobzon concert, what Kobzon, or did you
Кобзона что Кобзона или ходили вы
Kobzon concert, of course, soon
Кобзона конечно скоро
nabis, do you respect Kashpirovsky
набис так уважаете ли вы Кашпировского
ugh
тьфу
Lord
господи
[music]
[музыка]
someone sneezed Well, no, he didn’t sneeze
какой-то чихнул Ну всё нене не чихнул
so
так
uh, who do you believe more? Putin or
ээ кому больше верите Путину или
Solovyov,
соловьёву
of course Putin Solovyov, sometimes he makes such a
конечно Путину Соловьёв он порой такой
blunder what do you think Lord, how
ляпа ет что думаешь Господи как
[music] did
[музыка]
he understand?
ему понял
So if you are captured by the Ukrainians,
Так если вы попадёте в плен к украинцам
what will you say in  my
что вы скажете в своё
justification Well, I think God had mercy on me,
оправдание Ну я думаю меня Бог помиловал
I’m not captured
я в плен не
[music] I’m
[музыка]
captured
попадаю
so you respect Zyuganov
так Зюганова уважаете
Yes, but
Да а
Dugin Well, I don’t know Dugin much, so the
Дугина Ну я Дугина мало знаю поэтому
death penalty that Patriarch Kirill calls for
смертный казни к которым призывает
is normal, how do you
Патриарх Кирилл это нормально как вы к
feel about it that Patriarch Kirill
этому относитесь что Патриарх Кирилл
calls for the death penalty?
призывает смертные казни к которым
Patriarch Kirill calls on Is it normal
призывает Патриарх Кирилл Это нормально
or not, that is, he calls on yes, yes, it’s
или нет то есть он призывает да да
normal and I call on and the whole Russian people
нормально и Я призываю и весь народ
calls on it’s cool
призывает прикольно
so Zhirinovsky Loved that I love
так Жириновского Любили что я люблю
women
женщин
understood Israel
понял Израиль
support I somehow began to have a
поддерживаете я как-то к евреям стал
very very negative attitude towards Jews I understand
относиться очень очень отрицательно Поня
how you treat
как относитесь к ва
us  Grandfathers are fools Well, in a year or two they
дробим дедки дурачки Ну год-два они
will grow up and all this will pass. I understand how
вырастут и всё это пройдёт Поня как
we don’t have this in schools, so where I don’t
в школах у нас этого нет вот я где не
sleep there is Quadro at school. They say no. How do you
сшу есть в школе Квадро Они говорят нет
feel about the fact that in Russia they
А как вы относитесь к тому что в России
started mass persecution of these
вот там начали массовую травлю этих
Quadro-bers they say  so that they would be fined there in short,
Квадро беров говорят чтобы их там короче
no one is
штрафовали никто их не
persecuting them Maybe it’s Capital fashion,
травит Может это Столичная мода больше у
you don’t have it anymore in Belgorod, it’s still an infection But
вас в Белгороде нету это ещё зараза А у
you have all these people, you let them go from the farm,
вас же всех этих Вы же гори с фермы
Yes, you respect Kirkorov as a
выпустили Да так Киркорова уважаете как
people’s artist
народного артиста
Well
Ну
[music]
[музыка]
yes
да
So what?  in general, they ask how to
Так а как как вообще вот спрашивают как
find out that a person is Quadro
узнать что человек Квадро
Ber Well, first of all, who is Quadro?
Бер Ну кто вопервых кто такой Квадро
If you imagine that
Если вы представляете что
an eleventh grader will walk dog
одиннадцатиклассник будет ходить собач
mas and Nakah the floor on the sidewalk, this will not
мас и Наках пол по тротуару такого уж не
be the case, who will do this for first-graders, second
будет кто этим занима первоклашки второй
grade, no way Well, fools, then
класс да никак Ну дурачки то
fools, this class will pass Andrew
дурачки пройдёт этом клас ую Эндрю
asks why childless
спрашивает интересно почему бездетные
Golikova and Mizulina encourage women to
Голикова и мизулина призывают женщин
give birth to childless Golikova and who and
рожать бездетный Голикова и кто и и
Mizulina Well, first of all, I don’t know whether
мизулина Ну во-первых я не знаю
they are childless or I was interested, but in
бездетные они или интересовался а
general, they need to give birth to children. Why do
вообще-то Детей рожать надо А почему они
n’t they give birth themselves and tell others that
сами не рожают а другим расскажет что
let women
давайте бабы
give birth, who is it?  asks
рожайте кто это спрашивает
people people, go ask them Why don’t they
люди люди идите спросите у них Почему не
give birth, how do you feel about the fact that
рожают как относитесь тому что дети
Putin’s children live in
Путина живут в
Switzerland how many times has this
Швейцарии уже сколько раз про это
been said, they don’t live in
говорилось не живут они в
Switzerland, of
Швейцарии
course you didn’t think that war would come to your territory Well, I still
территорию конечно не думали Ну я же ещё
want to repeat myself, here’s the order No  There would
хочу повториться вот приказа Нет уже бы
n’t have been a single one in Kursk a long time ago; there’s no order; there’s already no one in
одной не было уже приказа нету уже в
their cauldron. Month Month Month Month And you
котле их Месяц Месяц Месяц Месяц А вы
still don’t leave, at least you
всё никак не уходите хотя бы мужиков
feel sorry for your guys.
парней своих пожалели
Well, you kept walking and walking; there are already thirty corpses of
Ну а вы всё шл и шл уже тридцатка трупов
yours
есть ваших
in such a small area. Nothing.  to yourself
на таком маленьком пятачке Ничего себе
These are the legs that are faster,
Вот это ноги быстрее
[ __ ] up,
капец
so Lisne asks how a woman can be
так лисне спрашивает как можно женщину
forced to give birth, this is
заставить рожать это
idiocy. Well, you can’t force it, but you
идиотизм Ну заставить то нельзя а
can stimulate it, but how to
стимулировать можно а как
stimulate it, how to stimulate it, give
стимулировать как стимулировать дать
an apartment, give financial support,
квартиру дать материальное обеспечение
give benefits Why Yes, look, well, it’s
дать льготы Почему Да вот смотрите ну
somehow interesting. On the contrary, in
как-то интересно Наоборот что в более
poorer countries  they multiply more strongly than
бедных странах размножаются сильнее чем
richer people, that is, people when of course.
более богатые то есть люди когда конечно
That is, after all, it’s not entirely connected with
То есть всё-таки это не совсем связано с
material things.
материальным
But why did it get dark for them, they
да А что у них потемнело они ночью
went to bed at night and sent the children to do something
ложаться и погнали детей делать
earlier in Russia, as was the case in the villages, there
раньше-то в России как было в деревнях
was no light, the sliver burned out and they
света не было лучинка перегорела и
drove  on the stove for the children Yes, but there
погнали на печку детей дела Да но там
was a problem In short, both the
была проблема В одной хате жили короче и
grandfather and the woman and a lot of people lived in the same hut How is it
дед и баба и куча народу Как там и
normal? There, on the stove, so many
нормально Там там на печке столько
people were lying there, not much shorter and without a
народу лежало там не сильно короче и без
splinter Normal Normal Maybe there
лучинки Нормально Нормально Может просто
was just no contraception and no
не было контрацепции и
idea then  and I had no idea
понятия то тогда и понятия не было
about this at all, yes Previously, someone lay on the stove
вообще об этом да Раньше кто на печке
and got pregnant yes
полежал тот и забеременел да
[music]
[музыка]
so what do you think the losses of the
так как вы считаете Какие потери армии
Russian army are? You say that Ukraine
РФ Вот вы говорите что Украина там
lost 30,000 there and in the Kursk region And
30.000 потеряла да в Курской области А
how much did Russia lose there? Yes, this is the
сколько Россия там потерял Да это
Ministry of Defense says  and
Министерство обороны говорит и говорит
Putin says so they say how many
Путин так говорят то сколько потеряно
108 tanks were lost, something armored vehicles know what
108 танков чтото броне машин знает че
How many Russians from chickens are in the Kursk region
Сколько в Курской области руски из кур
how many of yours how many of your soldiers
сколько ваших сколько ваших солдат
died in the Kursk
погибло в Курской
region I don’t know this figure 30,000
области мне эта цифра неизвестна 30.000
Ukrainians tell you
украинцев тебе говорят
so prestige asks how the people
так престижи спрашивает как народ
reacted to the bombing of alcohol
отреагировал на бомбёжку спирт
factories of whom  alcohol
заводов кого спирт
factories Where in
заводов Где в
Russia what kind of factory are alcohol factories
России какого завода спиртовые заводы
that Ukraine Bombed How do you feel about
что Украина Бомбила Как вы относитесь к
this
этому
I don’t
во не
understand
понял
Ukrainian Ukrainian drones bombed
украинские украинские дроны разбомбили
distilleries in the Russian Federation How do
спиртзаводы в Российской Федерации Как
you
вы к этому
feel about this And where they bombed one
относитесь А где разбомбили они один где
somewhere how do you feel about one in the aunt’s they
то как относитесь один в тёткино
bombed Yes, they pushed the men’s threshold
разбомбили Да мужиков порожек надавали
Is it really possible to bomb a distillery, well, you have to drink it,
разве можно спиртзаводы бомбить его ж
a special distillery was bombed
надо спецзавод разбомбили
Well,
Ну
the damned
Проклятые на святое
were soaring on the sacred, it’s better to hit the church, but
парились лучше лучше в в церковь ударили
rather than stealing the plant, it was possible to
да чем спер завод можно было ферму
destroy the farm Well, the distillery, well, this is sacred Yes, yes,
разбить Ну спиртзавод ну это святое Да
yes, they got caught for the sick Yes, I
да да за больное зацепили Да
wonder why Strelkov Girkin was imprisoned
интересно за что посадили Стрелкова
and what did he do?  I honestly don’t know, they
а что его я честно говоря не знаю
imprisoned Well, for what for statements
посадили Ну за что за высказывания
against the Russian army, how do you feel about
против российской армии как относитесь к
Alya
Але
Pugacheva? Well, as a performer, I
Пугачёвой Ну как к исполнительница
have a good attitude, but they forgot about molestation.
отношусь а как к растлении
Hai lives there somewhere in
забыли Хай там живёт у себя там где-то
there, she’s no longer of any use to anyone
там она уже никому не
[music]
[музыка]
Well,  songs
нужда Ну а песни
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
cool Artyom asks why Crimea and
классные Артём спрашивает почему Крым и
Donbass have the right to self-determination, but
Донбасс имеют право на самоопределение а
Chechnya
Чечня
doesn’t, and Chechnya probably does. So why did
нет да и Чечня наверное имеет Так почему
Chech, when Russia separated, attack
чеч тогда когда отделяла Россия напала
it,
на неё
some literate people? The Armed Forces ask this
какието грамотные люди ВС это задают
nsk war How did it
нска война С чего
begin when Russia Yes attacked  Russia
началась с того что Россия Да напала на
attacked Chechnya and
Чечню а взяла и
attacked Chechnya, but the
напала росия на Чечню напала а то что
Chechens started killing Russians in Chechnya,
чеченцы начали убить русских в Чечне
evicting them, starting
выселять выгонять начали поезда
stopping trains, robbing them, and so on and so
останавливать грабить и так далее и так
forth. Well, this is their country, so what do you
далее Ну так это ихняя страна сть что тя
mean if Chechnya wanted to be
себе это ж если Чечня захотела быть
another country? But  this is already a priest Hitler
другой страной А вот это уже попа Гитлер
says that everyone has a conger, no, well, look,
говорит конгер у всех ту не ну смотрите
for example, in Russia now they are detaining
например в России сейчас задерживают
some oppositionists And so on Yes,
каких-то оппозиционеров И так дальше Да
this is their business, and here Chechnya
вот это ихние дела так и тут Чечня - это
was a separate state, you attacked
отдельное государство было вы напали Да
And they returned it, that it was a separate
и вернули его что это было отдельно
state Well  so they have decided
государство Ну вот они определились
Because why the DPR LPR can go to Chechnya
Потому что почему ДНР лнр можно а Чечне
right away Why is there a specific state There was a
сразу Почему удельно государство Там был
president Yes, that’s
президент
right, he was the president Yes, the
Да правильно он был президентом Да
elected elected president of Chechnya
выбранным избранным президентом Чечни
was what kind of president was the
был каким
general general, that is, in short, all
генерал генерал то есть короче всякие
these people who were sent from Moscow to the DPR, in
эти которые из Москвы прислали в ДНР это
short, these people’s elected representatives there  Yes, and
короче народные там эти избранники да а
this is a people's criminal, he understood rey, so
это народный преступник понял рея так
let's move on Why don't you like woof
едем дальше Почему вы не любите гава
Why why don't you like
Почему почему не любите
Galkin Why don't you like Galkin And
Галкина Почему не любите Галкина А
why don't you like Maxim
почему не любите Максима
Galkin
Галкина
like Why why why
любите Почему
Putin smiled when he said
чему почему Путин улыбался когда говорил
that the submarine Kursk sank
что подлодка Курск утонула
said that the submarine Kursk
говорил что подлодка Курск
sank What about  It’s a little
утонула А что у нело
small that Sasha asks what the Soviet
мал что Саша спрашивает что Советский
Union did in Afghanistan and
Союз делал в Афганистане и
Angola, well, you see, I’m asking for
анголе ну Понимаете вот вот я прошу
forgiveness Well, illiterate Well, what can I
прощения Ну неграмотные Ну что я могу
say that the Soviet Union did the
сказать что Советский Союз сделал
Soviet Union came there by invitation
Советский Союз вол туда по приглашению
What was his name I forgot to be honest, he was
Как его звали забыл честно говоря его
invited there just like Bashar
пригласили туда точно также как Башар
Assad invited Russia to Syria and Russia
Асад пригласил Россию в Сирию и Россия
invited Russia here And the
сюда ла приглашён Росси А
question is Well, what can I
вопрос Ну что я могу
say [music] illiterately Swat How is
сказать неграмотно Сват Как так
it that all of Russia’s neighbors, who are
получается что все соседи России которые
small and non-nuclear, somehow
маленькие да об безъядерные они как-то
all attack Russia Georgia attacked
все нападают на Россию Грузия напала
Ukraine attacked And so on  how is it so?
Украина напала И так дальше как так
Where did Georgia attack? Well, Georgia
получается Куда Грузия напала Ну Грузия
attacked Russia. You said in 2008 that Russia attacked Georgia. Even the UN confirmed that
напала Да даже ООН подтвердила что
Georgia attacked. Well, let him read what I’m
Грузия напала Ну пускай читает то что я
asking, why is it that all
спрашиваю почему так получается что все
small countries without nuclear weapons are
маленькие страны без ядерного оружия
running to attack Russia?
бегут нападать на Россию
Yes, Abkhazia and Ossetia were, in general,
Да Абхазия и Осетия это были в общем-то
they were like those Yes, I see Why Ukraine
они как те Да я смотрю Почему Украина
is weak Georgia is weak Why did they
слабенькая Грузия слабенькая Почему они
attack Russia well how can it be
напали на Россию ну как так может быть
that a weakling attacked
чтобы Слабак напал на
strongly that how is it that
сильно что как так получается что
small countries Russia oh Ukraine
маленькие страны Россия ой Украина
Georgia attack Russia  well, how
Грузия нападают на Россию ну Какие
small are we noug Georgia Georgia Well with there
маленькие ны нуг Грузия Грузия Ну с там
3 ml or so Well where did she attack Georgia
3 мл или скоко Ну куда она напала Грузию
Well Georgia Georgia where did she attack Well the
Ну Грузия Грузия куда она напала Ну то
same thing Russia said Russia said that it
же Россия сказала Россия сказала что
attacked a peacekeeper there or something else
напала на миротворца там или ещё что-то
I don’t know they’ll come up with Yes on the
я не знаю там придумает Да на
peacekeepers  attacked, killed about n50
миротворцев напало поубивали около п50
people, skinned, yes And why did they attack
человек схили да А за Зачем напали на
Georgia
Грузию
then who attacked
тогда кто напал
Russia, the battle had already started there, the
Россия там уже началась битва там начали
Georgians had already started to destroy everything,
уже грузины начали вообще всё уничтожать
yeah, I got it, screw it, our fifty-eighth
Ага понял капец наша пятьдесят восьмая
army entered there under coercion and the world
армия туда вошла к принуждению и мир на
ended there, I got it, it’s
этом закончилось понял
cool All in short, that’s it  this is interesting, you
прикольно Все короче вот это интересно
know everything, Russia is being attacked by a nuclear power
все знаешь на Росси на ядерную державу
Cool
Прикольно
Well, some I'm
Ну какие-то я
holding
держа
uh have you seen the films of director Robert
э видели вы фильмы режиссёра Роберта
Magyar
мадьяра
they ask which director Robert
спрашивают какого режиссёра Роберта
Madr No, you don't understand Well, we'll
мадра Нет не ви понял Ну и будем уже
finish then I don't like the last
заканчивать потом я не люблю последний
question asks What is your favorite
вопрос спрашивает Какая ваша любимая
bottle Bye  yes, well, the last question
бутылка Пока да ну последний вопрос
asks What is your favorite
спрашивает Какая ваша любимая
bottle Well, let him sit on it and that’s what
бутылка Ну пускай он на неё сядет и вот
I’ll be Show it so we
этому я будет Покажите чтобы мы
can see
посмотрели
what everything is like so far We’re all running away
какая всё пока Всё разбегаемся
talking about the day of the Belgorod grandfather The
разговорились дня белгородского деда
revelation of this stream that it turns out the
Откровение этого стрима что оказывается
grandfather is not at home the grandfather of the month of August is sitting in a
дед не дома дед августа месяца сидит в
temporary accommodation center
пункте временного размещения
evacuated  it was just like
эвакуированный это просто это было как
a balm for the soul, really give a plus to
бальзам на душу реально поставьте плюсик
everyone who got high when they heard this Oh grandfather
все кто кайфанул когда это услышал О дед
who poured out poison for 2 C2 years
который 2 С2 года
How are the Ukrainians
ядом излива Как там украинцам там всё
doing everything right there yes the war came
своё правильно проходит да война пришла
to his house and he is now evacuated he is
в его дом и он теперь эвакуирован он
sitting somewhere in the point  temporary
сидит где-то в пункте временного
accommodation in Belgorod in
размещения в Белгороде в
the basement like subscribe comment and send it to
подвале лайк подписка комент и скиньте
everyone that the buzz will overtake them like this
всем что вот так их настигнет
subscribe to my Ista I don’t know
кайф подпишись на мий Иста Я не знаю для
why you are there to marvel at the
чего тоб для чого тоб там дивитись на
oce mi face Ale for you tse one two
оце мий фейс Але для тебе це один два
or three clicks and you three more men  and I'll
або три клика а ты тримае мене и я буду
say Wow in me there's a bunch of fouls and in
казати Вау в мене там Купа фолов и в
me there'll be a great mood to robiti but
мене буде класний настрий щоб робити но
cool video message on Instagram bye Andriy
крут вдео пись на й Instagram пок Андрий
like this let me
так давай я тебя
check for you and
чекаю а